{
    "subject": "resource/Arizona_Christian_University",
    "predicate": "property/country",
    "object": "resource/United_States",
    "human_readable": "Arizona Christian University is located in United States.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9884350299835205,
            "question": "Is Arizona Christian University located within the United States?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9656980037689209,
            "question": "Where is Arizona Christian University located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8919475674629211,
            "question": "In what country is Arizona Christian University situated?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8712704181671143,
            "question": "What is the geographical location of Arizona Christian University?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8457411527633667,
            "question": "Can you tell me the state where Arizona Christian University is found?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7168363928794861,
            "question": "To which nation does Arizona Christian University belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6583535671234131,
            "question": "Where in the world would you find Arizona Christian University?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6511951088905334,
            "question": "Is Arizona Christian University in a foreign country?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6471230387687683,
            "question": "What country houses Arizona Christian University?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5939736366271973,
            "question": "What continent is Arizona Christian University on?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Arizona Christian University is located in United States.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7336_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What country houses Arizona Christian University?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7336_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Arizona Christian University in a foreign country?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7336_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where in the world would you find Arizona Christian University?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7336_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7336_105.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7336_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7336_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7336_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7336_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7336_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7336_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7336_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7336_88.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7336_92.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because all documents contain the phrase \"located in Phoenix, Arizona, United States\" or similar phrases that indicate Arizona Christian University's location."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about the location of Arizona Christian University, stating it is \"located in Phoenix, Arizona, United States.\" Therefore, the triple \"Arizona Christian University is located in United States\" is supported by the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}